RG 170:001, Mansfield Training School
Connecticut State Library
- Series 14. Training, circa 1968-1984, undated
  - Dining skills training: Tape 1 (short version) Utensil use: Definitions; Maladaptive behaviors: Definitions; Training procedures: Training and reinforcement guidelines', video tape (Box 123)
  - Dining skills training: Tape II (short version) Guidelines for training and maintenance. Example of training token reinforcement maintenance, 1978 September; video tape (Box 123)
    Video tape for helical scan video recorders.
  - Dr. Fonda lecture: Mental age, video tape (Box 123)
  - First aid. Emergency procedures for non-medical staff: A training guide, video tape (Box 123)
  - Hartford Chamber Choir in concert -- December 1968. Robert Gronquist conducting (TV presentation - Channel 24), 1968 December; audio tape (Box 123)
  - MTS/Court tape, video tape (Box 123)
  - Teaching new skills part 1 VII", video tape (Box 123)
  - Teaching new skills Part 2 VIII, video tape (Box 123)
  - Yale on physical therapy hospital improvement program, 1968 March 18; video tape (Box 123)
  - Unidentified, 3 audio tapes (Box 123)
  - Unidentified, 3 video tapes (Box 123)
    1 video tape for helical scan video recorders.
  - Ask just for little things, film (Box 124)
  - I'll promise you a tomorrow, film (Box 124)
  - Meta-orffosis, 2 films (Box 124)
  - Vital signs: Part II Taking temperature, pulse and respiration, film (Box 124)
  - Body mechanics, film (Box 125)
  - Mentally handicapped children growing up, film (Box 125)
  - Pattern for change, film (Box 125)
  - Somebody waiting, 2 films (Box 125)
  - Teaching the mentally retarded a positive approach, film (Box 125)
  - Modern concepts of epilepsy, film (video) (Box Item 126)
  - Genesis, film (Box Item 127)
  - Modern concepts of epilepsy, film (Box Item 128)
  - Grand mal epilepsy: Diagnosis and management, film (Box Item 129)
  - A place among us, film (Box 130)
  - Raising a mentally retarded child at home, 1 sound disc (Box 131)
    Produced by the National Film Board of Canada.